[{"answer": "Poor my friend, was it our fault this happened to him? Did we do something wrong? Maybe it was our fault", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, so it was my fault, but not yours", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You damn right it isn't. You better not be carrying on laughing in that courtroom, funny man. Cause if you start getting all smar", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, you looking good. You look strong. You one fin", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What did he want", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Your marble rye", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, I became aware of a", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "A, uh", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Contest", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's right, the Bubble Boy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He's a boy who lives in a bubble", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "And then Mr. my friend gave you a used wheelchair", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "So you were the doctor on duty the night my friend died", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "And what's your occupation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What does a library cop do", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How long was his book overdue", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What do you call them", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "At the time, I was employed as a security guard in the parking lot at the Garden Valley Shopping Mall.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Haven't we had this conversation before", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I think we have", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, maybe we have.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "So what is the deal with the yard? I mean when I was a kid my mother wanted me to play in the yard. But of course she didn't have to worry about my next door neighbor my friend sticking a shiv in my thigh. And what's with the lockdown? Why do we have to be locked in our cells? Are we that bad that we have to be sent to prison, in prison? You would think the weightlifting and the sodomy is enough. So, anyone from Cellblock D", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'll talk slower. I'm kidding", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Murder one? Oooooo, watch out everybody. Better be nice to you. I'm only kidding sir", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Finale-Part-2.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Grand theft auto", "qsentId": 28}]